He led the last great outlaw raids !
The Cimarron Kid is a western film directed by Budd Boetticher.
Audie Murphy comes into his own as a Western star in this story.
Wrongly accused by crooked railroad officials of aiding a train heist by his old friends the
Daltons, he joins their gang and becomes an active participant in other robberies.
Betrayed by a fellow gang member, Murphy becomes a fugitive in the end.
Seeking refuge at the ranch of a reformed gang member, he hopes to flee with the man's
daughter to South America, but he's captured in the end and led off to jail.
The girl promises to wait.
Bill Doolin / The Cimarron Kid, played by Audie Murphy.
Carrie Roberts, played by Beverly Tyler.
Bitter Creek Dalton, played by James Best.
Cimarron Rose Adams (as Yvette Dugay), played by Yvette Duguay.
Dynamite Dick Dalton, played by John Hudson.
Red Buck, played by Hugh O'Brian.
The Cimarron Kid is a 1952 American western film directed by Budd Boetticher
and starring Audie Murphy, Beverly Tyler and Yvette Duguay.
It was  produced and distributed by Universal Pictures.